Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 40)
- Wing, Kenneth (Acting Dean)--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 41)
- Wing, Kenneth (Acting Dean)--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 42)
- Wing, Kenneth (Acting Dean)--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Call, David--Correspondence ("Blue Copies"), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Call, David--Vice President Congratulations Letters, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 10/25/94-10/26/94, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 3/29/94-3/30/94, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 10/26/93-10/27/93, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 10/26/93-10/27/93, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 4/7/93-4/8/93, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 10/28/92-10/29/92, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 4/29/92-4/30/92, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 10/31/91-11/1/91, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 5/2/91-5/3/91, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 10/11/90-10/12/90, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 5/3/90-5/4/90, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 10/19/89-10/20/89, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 5/3/89-5/4/89, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 11/2/88-11/3/88, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 5/3/88-5/4/88, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- CALS Advisory Council--Geneva 11/5/87-11/6/87, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 3/19/87-3/20/87, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- CALS Advisory Council--Long Island 10/7/86-10/8/86 (photo enclosed), 1986 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- CALS Advisory Council--Ithaca 5/1/86-5/2/86, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- CALS Advisory Council Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- CALS Advisory Council Spring/Fall Meeting Agendas, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- CALS Advisory Council Spring/Fall Meeting Agendas, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- CALS Advisory Council Spring/Fall Meeting Agendas, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- CALS Advisory Council Reports to Board of Trustees, 1981-1995 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- CALS Advisory Council Reports to Board of Trustees, 1981-1995 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- CALS Advisory Council Reports to Board of Trustees, 1981-1995 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies on Past Council Members, c1972-c1987 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 44)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 45)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 46)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 47)
- CALS Advisory Council--Biographies, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 48)
- CALS Advisory Council--Members, 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 49)
- CALS Advisory Council--Members, 1984-1990 (Box 60, Folder 50)
- CALS Advisory Council--Members, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 51)
- CALS Advisory Council--Members, 1994-1996 (Box 60, Folder 52)
- Deans' (Academic) Meeting Agendas, 1986-1994 (Box 60, Folder 53)
- Deans' (Academic) Meeting Agendas, 1986-1994 (Box 60, Folder 54)
- Deans' Council, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 55)
- Dean's Council, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 56)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Deans & Directors Meetings--Background Material, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Deans' Planning Group, 1991-1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Deans' Planning Group, 1991-1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Deans' Planning Group, 1991-1995 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Deans' Planning Group, 1991-1995 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Department & Section Chairs Agendas, 1981-1993 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Department & Section Chairs Agendas, 1981-1993 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Department & Section Chairs Agendas, 1981-1993 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Department & Section Chairs Agendas, 1981-1993 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Department & Section Chairs--Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Department & Section Chairs--Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Department & Section Chairs--Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Faculty Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Statutory Deans Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1990-1991 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Annual Activities Report to the Provost, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 35)
- Annual Report Instructions, c1980/c1990 (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Annual Report Materials, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 37)
- Annual Report Materials--Sent to Dept. Chairs, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 38)
- Annual Report Materials--Sent to Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 39)
- Annual Report Materials, 1988-1992 (Box 61, Folder 40)
- Annual Report Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 41)
- Annual Report Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 61, Folder 42)
- Annual Report--Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 43)
- Annual Report--Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 44)
- Annual Report--Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 45)
- Annual Report--Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 46)
- Annual Report--Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 47)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 48)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 49)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 50)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Annual Report--College of Agriculture & Life Sciences & Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Call, David--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec-Oct), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct-Aug), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Aug-July), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (June-May), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-Mar), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-Feb), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec-Nov), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Aug), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-June), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-Mar), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-Feb), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-Jan), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-Mar), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-Apr), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Apr-May), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (June-July), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jul-Sept), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-Mar), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-May), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-Jul), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jul-Aug), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct-Nov), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-Mar), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Apr-May), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-Jul), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jul-Sept), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct-Nov), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov-Dec), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-Mar), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-May), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-June), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-Aug), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Aug-Sept), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct-Nov), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 34)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov-Dec), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Feb-April), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (June-Aug), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Aug-Oct), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-March), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-April), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-July), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-Oct), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Dec), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-April), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May-June), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-Sept), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Oct-Dec), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (March), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (April), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (May), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (June), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-Aug), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov-Dec), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Feb), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Mar-June), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (July-Aug), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Oct), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Nov-Dec), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Jan-Aug), 1978 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Deans & Directors Meeting Minutes (Sept-Dec), 1978 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Publications: Agricultural Resources Commission--A Basis for Developing a Food & Agricultural Policy for New York State, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Publications: Agriculture in the Economy of New York State, The Role of (David Call), 1977 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute--Annual Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute--Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute--Annual Reports, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute--Annual Reports, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 41)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute--Annual Reports, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Publications: Boyce Thompson Institute, c1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Publications: Facts & Figures of the NYS College of Agriculture & Life Sciences, 1978-1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Publications: Integrated Pest Management--Reports from the 1989 IPM Research, Development and Implementation Projects in Fruit, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Publications: Integrated Pest Management--Reports from the 1989 IPM Research, Development and Implementation Projects inVegetables, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Publications: Integrated Pest Management--Reports from the 1989 IPM Research, Development and Implementation Projects in Dairy & Field Crops, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Publications: Integrated Pest Management--Reports from the 1989 IPM Research, Development and Implementation Projects in Ornamentals, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. I, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. I, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. II, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. II, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. II, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Publications: Proposal to National Sea Grant College Program, Revised Vol. II, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy, & Planning--Vice Chancellor for (Joseph Burke, Sherry Penney, Alden Haffner), 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy, & Planning--Vice Chancellor for (Joseph Burke, Sherry Penney, Alden Haffner), 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy, & Planning--Vice Chancellor for (Joseph Burke, Sherry Penney, Alden Haffner), 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy, & Planning--Vice Chancellor for (Joseph Burke, Sherry Penney, Alden Haffner), 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- SUNY--Academic Programs & Research--Vice Provost for (Richard Jarvis), 1991-1993 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Administrative Central Services--Deputy to the Chancellor of (James Lyng), 1987-1990 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Affirmative Action, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Agriculture & Technical Colleges, 1983-1989 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Agriculture & Technical Colleges to 4 Year Colleges--SUNY Plans, 1981-1986 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Agriculture & Technical Colleges to 4 Year Colleges--SUNY Plans, 1981-1986 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1987-1994 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1987-1994 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1987-1991 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Campuses, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Capital Facilities--Vice Chancellor for (Irving Freedman), 1983-1992 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Capital Facilities--Vice Chancellor for (Irving Freedman), 1983-1992 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Capital Facilities--Vice Chancellor for (Irving Freedman), 1983-1992 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Bruce Johnstone), 1988-1995 (Box 65, Folder 36)
- SUNY-- Chancellor, Senior Vice (Harry Spindler), 1987-1993 (Box 65, Folder 37)
- SUNY-- Chancellor, Senior Vice (Harry Spindler), 1987-1993 (Box 65, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Cornell Relations, 1980-1985 (Box 65, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Cornell Relations, 1980-1985 (Box 65, Folder 40)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1990-1994 (Box 65, Folder 41)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1990-1994 (Box 65, Folder 42)
- SUNY--Dean's Task Force, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 43)
- SUNY--Educational Services, 1983-1985 (Box 65, Folder 44)
- SUNY--Educational Technology--Vice Chancellor for (James Nall), 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 45)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1988-1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1988-1992 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- SUNY--Finance & Business--Vice Chancellor for (William Anslow), 1989-1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- SUNY--Finance & Business--Vice Chancellor for (William Anslow), 1989-1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations--Deputy to the Chancellor for (Herbert Gordon, James Ruhl), 1981-1992 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations--Deputy to the Chancellor for (Herbert Gordon, James Ruhl), 1981-1992 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations--Deputy to the Chancellor for (Herbert Gordon, James Ruhl), 1981-1992 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations--Deputy to the Chancellor for (Herbert Gordon, James Ruhl), 1981-1992 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, 1989-1993 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, Associate Vice Chancellor for (Thomas Freeman), 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- SUNY--International Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Minority Scholarships, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- SUNY--Provost (John Burke), 1987-1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Provost (John Burke), 1987-1994 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Provost (John Burke), 1987-1994 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Provost (John Burke), 1987-1994 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Provost (John Burke), 1987-1994 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Research & Economic Development, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Research, Graduate Studies, & Professional Programs, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Research, Graduate Studies, & Professional Programs, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- SUNY--Research, Graduate Studies, & Professional Programs, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Review Process for Chancellor & Presidents, 1974-1977 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- SUNY--State University Status, Proposed Amendments to, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Student Affairs & Special Programs Cabinet, Vice Chancellor for (Frank Pogue), 1987-1993 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Task Force on College Entry Level Knowledge & Skills, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Tenure Statements, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Transfer Policy, 1973/1990 (Box 66, Folder 31)
- SUNY--University Affairs & Development, Vice Chancellor for (Robert Perrin), 1982-1995 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- SUNY--University Affairs & Development, Vice Chancellor for (Robert Perrin), 1982-1995 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- SUNY--University Affairs & Development, Vice Chancellor for (Robert Perrin), 1982-1995 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- SUNY--University Counsel, 1985-1990 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- Outgoing correspondence, blue copies, January - June 1988 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Outgoing correspondence, blue copies, July - December 1988 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Outgoing correspondence, January - June 1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Outgoing correspondence, July - December 1989 (Box 67, Folder 4)